你飚得好快哦
Fast bike, huh?
是啊 还可以
Yeah, sometimes.
要加油吗？
Want me to fill it up?
我不是来加油的
I'm not here for the gas.
帮我看好我的车
You can keep an eye on it for me.
要算帐就到路上算
Leave it on the road, guys.
机车小子 你差点害我撞车
That stunt almost cost me my ride, boy.
- 我在赶时间 你挡了我的路 - 你赶着去投胎吧
- You were in my way. I was in a hurry. - Well, now you'll be late.
你的脏手别碰我的车
Hey! Get your dirty little punk ass off my car.
开车的人怎么都这么嚣张？
What is it about driving cars that makes you all such assholes?
你擦不擦车窗？
Can you do something about these dirty windows?
五块钱
Five bucks.
收十块钱吧
Make it 10.
谢啦
Thanks.
系好安全带
Buckle up.
你没两下就惹上麻烦了
Well. It didn't take long for you to find trouble.
尽管来 我免费招待你吃拳头
Step up. I'm running a two-for-one special today.
吃拳头？
Special, huh?
有送薯条吗？我饿扁了
Can I get fries with that? Because I'm hungry as hell.
- 福特 近来可好？- 见到你真好
- What's up, Ford? How you doing, boy? - Good to see you, man.
- 我也一样 - 欢迎回来
- Wish I could say the same for you. - Welcome home.
谢了 兄弟 威 道尔顿 你们又迟到了
Thanks, man. Val, Dalton. Late as usual.
这小子一声不响跑去泰国半年 还敢嫌我们
Dude's gone six months in Thailand without a word and now he's busting our chops.
你们怎么变得这么难伺候？
Since when did you get so sensitive?
我得赶去参加机车大会
I got a rally to get to.
你一定是想去送死
You must be in a hurry to die.
亨利他们看到你 肯定不爽
Henry James and his boys aren't gonna be as happy to see you as we are.
- 你不是在逃亡 干嘛回来？- 我得把事情解决掉
- You were on the run. Why you back now? - I gotta make things right.
我一直忘不了她
I couldn't stop thinking about her.
- 我以为你是忘不了我们 - 听好…
- And here I thought it was alI about us. - Look...
这是我惹的麻烦 你们不必被拖下水
this is my mess, not yours. You don't have to make this run.
- 你一个人搞不定 - 你需要我们
- We can't let you have all the fun. - You're gonna need us.
没错
Yes, I am.
你还会骑车吧？
Still know how to ride that thing?
来比一比就知道啰
We'll have to race the twisties to find out.
福特 你到底想干嘛？
Ford, what the hell are you doing?
我想看你被我超车的衰样
I don't want to miss that look on your face when I blow past you.
搞什么？
What the ?
- 有人追上来了 - 滚开 臭小子
- We got company. - Out of my way, punk!
他有毛病吗？
What's his problem?
让我来
I got him!
- 你死定了 - 放马过来
- Your ass is mine. - Let's go, punk.
你行吗？
Come on, what you got?
- 怎样？- 有本事来呀
- You like that? - Bring that piece of shit on.
我烧起来了…
I'm burning, I'm burning.
- 别冲动 - 烧死他最好
- Relax! - You should've let him burn!
他差点害死我们
He could've killed us!
小子 咱们走着瞧 让开
Hey, punk, we ain't done yet. Move out of the way.
让我看这小子有什么能耐
Let's see if this guy fights as bad as he rides.
- 滚吧 - 大嘴巴…
- Walk away. - You got loud pipes...
别光说不练
but you ain't saying nothing!
你不会有好下场的
You ain't gonna like how this ends.
这下你死定了 白小子
It's your turn to burn, white boy.
朱利尔 你掉了东西
What's up, J? Drop something?
我会搞定他们 老大
Just taking care of some business, T.
福特 听说你跑到东南亚吃寿司
Ford. I heard you was up in Indochina eating sushi and shit.
- 寿司不是日本才有吗？- 我知道啦 臭小子
- I thought sushi came from Japan. - I know where sushi come from, nigga.
我又没在问你
I ain't even talking to you.
我大可以把你揍扁
You know I could smash you right now.
还有你的小啰喽
You and your little tricycle friends.
不过我就放你一马
But I'm gonna give you a pass.
算是欢迎你回来
Consider it a welcome-home present.
只有一个条件 赔我小弟一台新机车
Under one condition. Somebody gonna give my brother a new bike.
- 我要他的车 - 想得美
- I want his bike. - I ain't giving you shit.
想要机车就放马过来
There's only one way you're getting one of these bikes.
我知道你离开了很久 福特
I know you been gone a long time, Ford.
但不至于忘了这儿谁是老大
But not long enough to forget who run things around here.
小心我拿你去喂狗
I hate to see you end up as Dojo's dinner.
老大 有警察
Trey. One-time.
现在不是喂狗的好时候
Probably not a good time to be feeding Dojo anything, huh?
改天再找你算帐
Get that bike from you later.
警察伯伯 你好吗？
Hey, officer, how's it going?
今天天气真好
Beautiful day today.
- 你还在等什么？- 你觉得怎样？
- What are you waiting for? - What you think?
让他们瞧瞧你的厉害
Go show these boys how to ride.
- 载我一程怎样？- 我会让你受不了
- How about a ride? - This thing might be too much for you.
- 没试过 不知道 - 你们够了吧
- We'll never know till I'm on it. - All right, you too.
我先走一步啰
It's not that I don't enjoy your company.
对他温柔点
Just be gentle with him.
- 好帅的机车 - 好翘的屁股
- Nice bike. - Nice ass.
你有名字吗？
Got a name?
有啊
Yeah.
福特 他跑来干嘛？
Ford. What's he doing here?
天气预报 今天阳光普照
Forecast for today sun, sun and more sun.
华氏94到103度 记得擦防晒油
Highs 94 to 103. Don't forget your sunscreen, folks.
西南风时速10到15里…
Southwest winds 10 to 15 miles per hour, with locally higher gusts.
请稍等一下
Be with you in a second.
要找什么吗？
Looking for something in particular?
你有没有粉红色皮座椅？镶金边的？
Yeah, you got one of them seats in a pink Naugahyde? Maybe with a little gold fringe?
你从来都不会搞笑
You never were funny, Ford.
你以前觉得我很搞笑
Oh, come on, you used to think I was funny.
也许你失去幽默感 夏恩
Maybe you lost your sense of humor.
我还是很有幽默感呀
I think I have a pretty good sense of humor.
就像你那天早上一落跑 联邦探员就拿着搜票冲进店里…
Like the morning you skipped town before agents raided my shop...
说我男友是个毒贩？
waving warrants, telling me my boyfriend's a drug dealer?
超搞笑的 我笑了几个礼拜
That was funny. I laughed my ass off for weeks.
我有写信给你
I wrote you letters.
- 我把信给烧了 - 我打过电话给你
- I made fires. - I tried to call.
这半年来我的电话被监听 这也很搞笑
Yeah, but my phone was tapped for six months. That was fun too.
- 听我解释 - 让我猜猜
- Can I explain? - Let me guess.
你很抱歉 你不是故意伤害我 你只是想保护我
You're sorry, you didn't mean to hurt me, you were trying to protect me...
- 而且这不是你的错 - 这是我的错
- and it wasn't your fauIt. - It was my fauIt.
- 打烊了 - 可是招牌说…
- We're closed. - The sign said...
招牌写错了 谢了
Well, the sign lied. Thanks.
你也走吧
You too, Ford.
我一直在想该怎么跟你解释
You don't know how many times I've played this out in my head in the last six months.
你一定把脑袋都想破了
Must be frustrating.
算你有种回来
You got balls even coming here.
联邦探员跟地狱帮都在找你 亨利认为你偷走他的机车
The feds and the Hellions are after you and Henry James thinks you stole his bikes.
是啊
Yeah.
因为那是真的
Well, that's because I did.
- 福特 - 干嘛？
- Ford? - Yeah?
- 快走吧 否则… - 否则怎样？
- Go now, please, before I... - Before what?
我们本来决定要去海滩玩
And to think we almost decided to go to the beach this weekend.
幸好小路不喜欢游泳
Lucky for me, Luther hates to swim.
亨利
Henry.
你不必买新的座椅 福特
I don't know why you're buying a new seat, Ford.
旧的湊合着用就好了
Looks like you haven't broken in your old one yet.
看来福特爱用贱货
Looks like Ford prefers to ride bitch to me.
看来你最好也换一个新货 亨利
It looks to me like you ought to buy a new seat yourseIf, Henry.
老跟兄弟合用会染上怪病
Share one with your friends long enough and you're liable to catch something.
听说你去了东南亚
Heard you were in Indochina.
鸟不生蛋的地方
Some shit like that.
- 食物好吃吗？- 我是去泰国
- Good food there? - Thailand, actually...
食物超棒 多谢关心
but the food was great. Thanks for asking.
你真会装蒜 福特
You're a pretty funny guy, Ford.
别装了…
Tell me...
给我老实说
you got a punch line for this
我的机车呢？
Where are my goddamn bikes?
你真的想要那些机车…
You really want them...
还是那里面的货？
or what's inside them?
在哪里？
Where are they?
- 跟他分吧 - 他才不会
- Why don't you just cut it out of him. - No, he won't.
他聪明的很
He's too smart for that.
他知道他一碰我就拿不到货
Because he knows if he touches me he'll never get his shit back.
也许…
Then again...
我没那么聪明
I'm not that smart.
夏恩
Shane.
限你在日落前交出我的机车
You've got till sundown to hand over my bikes.
- 你老弟答应跟我合作 - 朱利尔不能作主 我才是老大
- Your brother said we had a deal. - Junior don't do the deals around here, I do.
他不能作主 就不该乱放话
Well, if Junior ain't allowed to make deals, he shouldn't be allowed to speak.
真巧 我也有同感
That's funny, because I was thinking the same thing.
我不是来看你逗狗 黑猩猩
I didn't come here to watch you pet your dog, primate.
我也没请你这臭白人来
I didn't invite your Dukes of Hazzard ass.
快从我眼前消失 我不会答应你的
So you can raise up whenever you feel it. The answer is no.
你不能在我的地盘贩毒
You're not slinging your dope on my streets.
香槟拿给我
Hand me that bottle.
给我听好…
Look...
我不是街头小混混
I'm not some dimebag street punk.
我是生意人
I'm a businessman.
你最好识相点
And I'm telling you to make this right.
就算你是教父我也不甩你
I wouldn't give a shit if you was Don Corleone himseIf.
我的答案还是不
The answer is still no.
给我滚远一点
So get out of my face.
你在看什么？
What the hell was you looking at?
我爱你
I love you.
拜托 你干嘛不答应他？
Trey, what's wrong? I thought you would've been down with that shit.
我们可以海捞一票
You could've made a killing.
你觉得你闯的祸还不够多吗？
First you gonna act a fool up there on the road, now this?
你有什么毛病啊？
What's wrong with you?
别给我找麻烦
You messing with my goddamn good nature, boy.
去买啤酒来 少惹我
Go get me a beer, man. You messing up my buzz.
我要健怡可乐 别甩车门
Get me a Diet Pepsi. Don't slam my door.
你最好别冲动
You better count to 10!
- 我要好好教训他 - 闭嘴 叫伙计跟着他
- I'm gonna whup his ass. - Shut up. Put Rasan and Nomo on him.
连小狗嘟嘟都比他聪明
Dojo got more sense than that boy.
亨利 看来你被他耍了
Henry, looks like you're the one riding bitch.
- 你的引擎该修一修了 - 福特
Looks like your engine could use a little work.
我都说我不爱你 你是混球
What part of "I don't love you anymore, you're a bastard
我不想见到你 你还不死心？
and I never wanna see you again" didn't you understand?
因为你见到我并没有转头就走
How about the part that stops you from driving off right now?
渴了吗？
Thirsty?
一瓶啤酒 你请客
All right, one beer. But you're buying.
-朱利尔 你还好吗？-我一点也不好 滚开
- What up, Junior? You all right? - No, I'm definitely not all right, man. Move!
敢撞我 白小子
Watch out, white boy.
- 我是不小心的 - 小心我踢扁你
- Call it an accident? - How about I kick your ass?
我说我是不小心的
No, I prefer we still call it an accident.
- 不小心的？- 你欠我一罐啤酒
- How about now? - Now it looks like you owe me a beer.
- 朱利尔 - 我要宰了你
- Junior! Junior! - I'm gonna kill you!
住手
Come on, chill!
给我过来 你怎么老是给我找麻烦？
I'm gonna talk to you. Why you always got to show your ass, man, huh?
你为什么不能安份一点？
Why you can't come here and play your position?
看着我 小子
Look at me, boy.
我爱你 因为你是我老弟 可是别一直丢我的脸
I love you. You're my brother, but you better stop embarrassing me.
别这么毛毛燥燥
Stop acting so damn crazy.
我会照顾你一辈子
And I got your back for life.
照顾我 那就替我出口气 帮帮我呀
Well, if you got my back, then show me, blood, on everything!
你一点都不照顾我 我才不靠你呢
You ain't got my back, man. You ain't got my back, Trey. Forget you, man.
小心 给我让开
Watch out. Get out of my way, man.
白小子差点把你老弟揍扁
Dawson's Creek almost beat your brother's ass, blood.
闭嘴 去牵我的狗
Shut up, man. Go get my dog.
- 你要怎么对付福特？- 朱利尔 给了我灵感
- What're we gonna do about Ford? - Junior just solved our problem.
- 不如把福特抓起来 - 还不行
- Why don't we just grab him right now? - No, not now.
我有更好的主意 叫大伙儿来
I got a better idea. Get the boys.
你是怎么搞的？你一出现就会惹出一堆麻烦
What is it with you, Ford? Everywhere you go, everything turns to hell.
我就是有这本事
Yeah, it's a talent I have.
柴娜 去补补妆
Go powder your nose, China.
咱们玩玩吧
Let's have some fun.
- 是他 去逮他 - 他在那儿
- That's him. Get him. - There he is.
多谢地狱帮砸了这场子 我要走人了
We'd like to thank the Hellions for messing up another gig. I'm out of here.
他逃不了
He ain't going anywhere.
- 他来了 - 又走了 去抓他
- Here he comes. - There he goes. Get him!
散人啦 朱利尔
See you, Junior.
怎么回事？
Hey, what's up, man?
Hey. What's up?
老兄
Hey, dude.
该死
Damn!
你把我害惨了 朱利尔
You screwed me, Junior.
你这小子说话不算话
I assume you're apologizing for setting up a deal you couldn't do.
害我白白答应别人
I made promises based on your black ass.
现在问题可大了
And now I've got a problem.
- 你得要帮我解决 - 老兄
- But you're gonna help me out of it. - Yo, dog.
给我一些时间 我去劝崔瑞把事情搞定
Just give me time. I'm gonna talk to Trey. We could work this out, man.
我可以的
I could make this happen, all right?
你没时间了
Time's up.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do, baby?
曼谷到芭达尼有一条沿海公路
There's this one road that winds up the coast from Bangkok to Pattani.
一边是山 一边是大海
It's got mountains on one side, ocean on the other
骑车时好像可以把脚泡到海水里
so close sometimes it feels like you can just drag your foot in it.
我每次骑在路上就想到你
I tell you, the last six months, every time I took that drive I thought about you.
你想向我促销泰国旅游行程？
Did you come all this way to sell me a trip to Thailand?
一瓶啤酒的时间让你解释
You got to the bottom of this beer. Explain away.
好吧
All right.
我一年前认识亨利 我不喜欢他 不过他是客人
First met Henry about a year ago. I didn't like him, but he was a paying customer.
我替他修过车
I fixed his chopper a couple times.
半年前他带两台机车到你的店…
Six months ago, he turns up at your shop...
他要我替他保管几天
with these two bikes. He asked me if I'd mind looking after them.
我想一想无所谓
I figure, what the hell, right?
所以就答应他
So I do.
我去热车却发动不了 所以就检查油箱
Then I go to move them, they don't start. So I check the tanks.
发现里面装满安非他命
They're filled with kilos of crystal meth.
我就想先把机车弄走
So first thing, I get them out of there.
怪不得联邦探员会来搜我的店
So that's why that fed McPherson raided my shop after you split.
你也从地球上消失
And you dropped off the face of the Earth.
我之所以走…
I took off...
是不想把你拖下水
so that you wouldn't get dragged into it.
只要我一走
I split.
警方就以为只有我跟亨利同伙
Now I'm the only one involved with Henry.
你走是为了保护我？
So you left to protect me?
你是怎么想的？你可以回来把一切解释清楚…
What'd you think, you were gonna just come back and explain everything...
然后再跟我远走高飞？
and then we'd just ride off into the sunset together?
差不多吧
More or less.
你差不多想去哪里？
Well, which is it? More or less?
我想去墨西哥
Well, I was actually thinking Mexico.
- 别坏了我的好事 - 把衣服穿好
- You're killing me. - Get your gear on.
- 现在不行 - 咱们去墨西哥 夏恩一起去
- Not a good time. - Heading to Cabo. Shane's coming.
- 真的假的？- 真的
- Damn, really? - Yeah.
- 等我十分钟 - 快一点
- Give me 10 minutes, all right? - Come on.
让开
Move.
让开 让开
Move, man! Move!
可恶
Damn!
他是我小弟
Wait. That's my brother, man.
没关系
It's all right.
不 我要带你走
Oh, no. No, man. I'm taking him with me.
不行
You can't do that, son.
我们要查出真凶
Now, we're gonna find out who done this.
如果你知道谁杀死你小弟…
If you have any ideas who would want to kill your brother
如果我知道是谁 他早就没命了
If I knew who did this, you'd have two dead bodies right now.
有一个人声称看到凶手
We got a witness. Says she saw the whole thing.
二十来岁白人 骑着重型机车
A white male, mid-20s, rode a custom motorcycle.
- 身穿黑橘色皮衣 - 黑橘色皮衣？
- Wore black and orange leathers. - Black and orange leathers?
你知道这个人吗？
Hey, you know somebody who fits that description?
不再知道了
Not anymore.
走吧
Let's go!
联邦调查局 扫黑专案小组麦费森探员
FBI. Agent McPherson, federal gang task force.
我是邦恩警长 你不太像联邦探员
Sheriff Barnes. You don't look like your typical fed.
你以为应该长什么样？烂西装 破汽车 落伍发型？
What'd you expect? A cheap suit, late-model Taurus, a $10 haircut?
你们怎么这么快就赶到？
How did you all get here so fast?
这地方有这么多飚车族
Get this many motorheads in one place, all wearing color
迟早会出事 所以我早就来了
something's bound to happen. Pays to be close.
这位是韩德森探员
Oh, this is Agent Henderson.
别以为她是花瓶 她是最顶尖的探员
Don't let her good looks fool you. She's one of the best field operatives.
对不起 接个电话
Excuse me, I have to take this.
- 嗨 宝贝 我在办案 - 什么状况？
Yeah. Hi, baby. I'm at a crime scene right now.
- 典型凶杀案 - 典型凶杀案？
- It's a typical homicide. - Typical homicide?
什么是所谓的典型凶杀案？
Maybe you can explain to me what a typical homicide is.
我会搞定的 我保证
All right, I'll take care of it. Yeah, I promise.
- 有一个目击证人 - 是吗？
- I've got an eyewitness. - You do?
- 对 - 你这不就破案了？
- Yeah. - You've practically got this solved.
我也爱你 天啊
I love you too. Jesus Christ.
找到凶器 证人看到整个事件
We've got the murder weapon and she saw the whole thing.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
就算要把整个加州翻遍
I don't care if we have to comb every inch of California.
都要找到福特那小子 我在午夜前一定要拿他喂小狗
I want that boy Ford, and I want his head in Dojo's bowl by midnight.
- 知道吗？- 知道
- Amen? - Amen.
来吧 狗狗
Come on, boy.
付现金要押身份证影本
Motel policy for cash customers.
杰
Jay.
- 找到他了 - 臭小子
- Got him. - Son of a bitch.
- 我半年前就想逮他 - 他很帅
- I tried to pop Ford six months ago. - He's cute.
你可以去探监 地图
You can visit him in prison. Map.
你太会吃才会把自己吃穷
That's why you broke, you eat too much.
- 我来付 - 没关系
- I got it. - That's okay.
你打算用什么付帐？你帅气的笑容吗？
What were you planning on paying with, your good looks or your smile?
我喜欢强悍一点的妞儿
I love a girl who can take care of herself, man.
为了她 我也会回来
I would have come back too.
失陪一下
If you boys will excuse me.
我得去厕所补补妆
It seems like I'm overdue for some paint and bodywork myseIf.
你打算怎么对付亨利？你心里有个谱吧？
So, what are you gonna do about Henry? We got a plan, right?
等风头过了 我会说出机车下落
Yeah, once we're in the clear, I'm gonna tell Henry where he can pick up his shit.
不过呢…
Of course...
我也会通知麦费森探员
I'm also gonna call that punk McPherson and tell him.
让他逮到亨利 人赃俱全
Arrange a get-together with the evidence.
这样就皆大欢喜 对吧？
That way everybody gets what they deserve, right?
亨利拿到货 麦费森逮到亨利
Henry gets his shit, McPherson gets Henry
我们到墨西哥喝个烂醉
and we all go to Mexico and get drunk.
绰号朱利尔的死神帮飚车族
As I reported earlier, Wallace, a member of an Inglewood motorcycle gang
昨晚被人用机车链条勒毙
the Reapers, was brutally murdered last night with a motorcycle chain.
警方根据目击证人描述锁定嫌犯
With the help of an eyewitness, the FBI has come up with a suspect
年近三十的白人男子卡利福特
Cary Ford, a white male in his late 20s.
骑一台黑色重型机车
Ford was last seen riding a black custom motorcycle
身穿黑橘色皮衣
wearing orange and black racing leathers.
如果观众知道嫌犯下落…
If you have any idea as to his whereabouts...
请尽速和警方联络
please contact the local authorities.
卡利福特是重大命案的主嫌
Cary Ford is now the prime suspect in the murder of Junior Wallace.
打给警长
Call the sheriff, Hal.
有人在孤松镇看到福特
Ford was just spotted at Lone Pine.
上路吧
Let's drive a little.
喂
Yeah.
- 警方无线电说有人找到白小子 - 谁？
- Heard on the scanner they spotted the white boy. - Who
- 杀你小弟的白小子 - 地图给我
- Dawson's Creek, the white boy. - All right, get me a map.
我们要抄小路
We gotta make up some time.
- 喂 - 我找福特
- Yeah? - Give me Ford.
福特 找你的
Ford. It's for you.
- 我是福特 - 计划改变
- Ford. - Change in plans.
你朋友朱利尔挂了
Seems your buddy Junior's dead.
FBI 认为是你干的
Feds think you did it.
死神帮也说凶手是你 大家都认为人是你杀的
Reapers think you did it. Hell, everybody thinks you did it.
只要你交出货 我就能让你脱身
You tell me where my stuff is and it all goes away.
我不听别人命令
I don't take orders, Henry.
- 从前和以后都不会 - 什么？
- Never have, never will. - What's that?
你听过恶有恶报这句俗语吗？
Ever heard that what you put out comes back tenfold?
你在"支那"待太久了 那是什么意思？
You spent too much time in Chink Land, Ford. What does that mean?
你大限来时我可不想在你旁边
It means I don't wanna be next to you when the shit hits the fan.
而且"支那"是中国
And by the way, Henry "Chink Land" implies China.
我是在泰国 是不同的国家
I was in Thailand, it's a different country.
我的手机
Hey, my phone!
别动
Hold it right there.
大家趴下来
Everybody down on the ground!
别开枪
Quit shooting!
你找错人了
You got the wrong guy.
等警长来再说
We'll let the sheriff sort it out when they get here.
- 你没事吧？- 我搞定他们了
- Are you okay? - I got it under control!
我没有杀人
I didn't kill anybody.
妈的
Shit!
你是厄尔吗？
You Earl?
你做的早餐超好吃
Loved your French toast.
- 趴下来 - 我就说…
- Down. - Like I said...
- 我喜欢悍一点的妞儿 - 谢了
- I love a girl who can take care of herseIf. - Thanks.
你上了新闻 跟你打架的小黑 他挂了
You're on the news. That guy you got in a fight with is dead.
- 亨利要拿回他的毒品 - 你怎么不还给他？
- Henry set me up. He wants his drugs back. - Why don't you give them back.
- 不行 那是我唯一的保障 - 昨晚我们一起
- I can't. It's the only insurance I got. - You were with me last night.
- 你有不在场证明 - 趴下来 厄尔
I'm your alibi. Down, Earl!
去跟警察说呀
Tell the cops.
警察不是唯一的麻烦
Right now it ain't the cops that I'm worried about.
情况不妙
Not good.
- 死神帮来了 - 他说的对 夏恩
- Reapers! - He's right, Shane.
待会再说行吗？
You think we could finish this conversation later?
好吧 脱了险你就要报警 好吗？
All right. Once we're in the clear, you call the cops. Agreed?
我拿这个干嘛？
What should I do with this?
就当我没说过我喜欢悍妞
Forget what I said about liking women who can take care of themselves.
抱歉 事情不太妙 你留下来比较安全
Sorry, it's gonna get crazy. You'll be safer here than running with us.
- 回洛杉矶再见 - 你要我干嘛？
- See you back in L.A. - What am I supposed to do?
陪厄尔吗？
Hang out with Earl?
他们往哪儿走？
Which way?
快给我说 老头
Which way did you say, old man?
- 哪个方向？- 抄小路
- Which way? - Shortcut!
逮到他们就宰了他们
Let's catch them, kill them and bury them!
他们追上来了 该死 越来越多人
They're still on us! Shit! There's more of them!
- 怎么办？- 要往哪儿？
- What are we gonna do, Ford? - Where we going?
我正在想
I'm working on it!
他们走哪边？
Which way did they go?
可恶 走吧
Damn! Come on!
可以报警了吗？
Now can we call the cops?
- 不行 - 为什么？
- No. - Why not?
不只是警察 是麦费森
Because it's not just the cops, it's McPherson.
麦费森？
McPherson?
抄你店的家伙
The guy that tore up your shop.
他认为我是毒贩
He already thinks I'm a drug dealer.
现在又认为我杀死朱利尔 所以我一定要证明…
Now he thinks I shot Junior. And he has no reason to think otherwise...
- 自己无罪 - 真倒霉 链条断了
- unless I can prove it. - Bad just turned to worse. Bent link.
真是屋漏偏逢连夜雨
This just keeps getting better and better.
我的工具箱有备用链条
I got a spare in my toolkit.
他是被勒死的
He was strangled, by the way.
- 谁？- 朱利尔 是被机车链条勒死
- Who? - Junior. He was strangled with a bike chain.
妈的
Shit.
是亨利用自己的机车链条
Henry used the chain off his own bike.
- 你怎么知道？- 是啊 你怎么知道？
- How do you know that? - How do you know?
你怎么会知道的？
Yeah, how did you know that?
这个嘛…
Well, it's....
事情有点复杂
It's complicated.
- 你不左转就会去俄勒冈 - 应该右转
- You turning left, or we going to Oregon? - It's right.
右转？怎么？
It's right? What...?
别乱指我 我知道路
Get the finger out of my face. I know where I'm going.
亨利这下死定了
Henry just screwed himseIf.
- 你看到这些刮痕吗？- 嗯
- See those scratches and nicks? - Yeah.
这是齿盘刮出来的
Well, it picks them up from the sprocket.
每一台机车的刮痕都不同
Now, no two bikes got the same chain-wear pattern...
因为每个齿盘的磨损痕迹都不同
because no two sprockets are the same.
只要能证明亨利的链条是凶器
So we match the chain used to kill Junior with Henry's bike...
就能逮到他
and we got him.
就跟指纹一样
Like a fingerprint.
就连你这白痴也搞懂了耶
Try not to move your lips so much when you think.
现在可以报警了吧？
Now we call the cops, right?
可以了
Now we call the cops.
- 好恶心哦 - 去开房间吧
- Real cute, guys. - Get a room.
- 麦费森？- 福特 你越来越厉害了
- McPherson, it's F... - Ford. Looks like you're trading up.
从毒贩变成一级谋杀犯
Going from drug trafficking to first-degree murder.
- 我被人陷害 - 这句话我常听
- I was set up. - In my business I hear that a lot.
- 大声点 我正在侧录 - 谁会想陷害你？
- Loud. Recorder's on. - Who wants to set you up?
亨利
Henry James.
地狱帮老大 为什么呢？
Leader of the Hellions. Now, why would he wanna do that?
你要找的毒品是他的
Those drugs you were looking for belong to Henry.
你去抄店前一晚 我把货藏起来 亨利要讨回去
I stashed them the night before you raided the shop. He wants them back.
说出毒品下落 也许我会相信
Tell me where the drugs are, I might buy that'd give Henry motive.
- 也许我能让你脱罪 - 也许还不够好 把亨利抓起来
- Maybe we can work something out. - "Maybe" don't cut it. Arrest Henry...
- 我就交出毒品 - 逮捕他？凭什么？
- then I'll take you to the drugs. - Arrest him? On what grounds?
一级谋杀罪
First-degree murder.
- 我能证明凶器出于亨利之手 - 不太可能
- What if I tie the murder weapon to Henry? - Big "if"
逮捕他
Arrest him.
- 去拿他的车 我就把毒品交给你 - 去拿他的车 好
- Get his bike, I'll show you. - Get his bike. Okay.
你还要我逮捕谁呢？前女友 小学老师？
Anyone else you'd like me to arrest? Ex-girlfriend, second-grade teacher...?
- 等一下 我抄下来 - 你有没有在听
- Hold on, I'm making a list. - You're not listening to me.
- 亨利杀死朱利尔 - 我才不信
- Henry killed Junior. - I don't know that.
那你就帮不了我
Then you can't help me!
这方法不管用
Well, that didn't fly.
管它的 咱们去墨西哥吧
Screw it. Let's haul ass down to Mexico and don't look back.
这次我也同意
As much as I hate to say it, I agree with him.
- 我们要回洛杉矶 - 你这是自投罗网
- We're going to L.A. - Oh, yeah. That makes sense.
我要靠亨利的毒品替我脱罪
I have to get Henry's bike. That will clear me.
每条路都会有警方临检站
They'll have checkpoints on every dirt road between here and the coast.
骑重型机车太招摇了
We're not exactly hard to spot driving these.
- 你想把机车丢掉？- 不 骑车比较快
- You wanna ditch the bikes? - No, I'd rather be fast than invisible.
如果太容易就不好玩 对吧？
Come on. Wouldn't be any fun if it was easy, right?
我从不担心下一公里会怎样
I live my life a quarter mile at a time.
这是我听过最蠢的话
That is the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
每条公路都有警方临检站
Po-po got the highways blocked from here to L.A.
洛杉矶？
L.A.?
他怎么会笨到自投罗网？
Why would he go to the one place he know I got on lockdown?
- 咱们在州际公路堵他 - 他没那么笨
- Let's catch him on the interstate. - No, he's smarter than that.
他想偷溜回去
He trying to backdoor us.
一定会穿过沙漠
He going through the Palms.
我就会走那儿 去堵他吧
That's the way I'd go. And that's the way we going.
亨利去年因为持有毒品入狱
You know, Henry James did pull six months in L.A. County last year for possession.
也许福特说的有道理
Maybe Ford is onto something.
那你就帮不了我
Then you can't help me!
叫警方检查前往洛城的每条路
Call in. Check everything from Lone Pine and L.A.
- 福特真的会回洛杉矶？- 他要回去找亨利
- You think Ford's going back to L.A.? - He's going after Henry James.
如果是我被人陷害 我就会回去 走吧
If he's right and Henry did set him up, that's what I'd do. Let's go!
- 你没付油钱 - 对喔
- You have to pay for the gas. - Oh, right.
死神帮
Reapers!
- 我们在沙漠甩掉他们 - 你疯了吗？
- We'll lose them in the Palms! - Are you crazy?
我最讨厌他这样
I hate it when he does this!
- 他们骑进树林 - 我看到了 紧跟着福特
- They going into the trees! - I could see that, fool! Stay on Ford.
- 我快逮到他了 - 他们开枪了 福特
- I got his ass! - They're shooting at us, Ford!
- 我知道 - 怎么办？
- I know! - What do we do?
你往右 他们只会追我
Go right! They'll follow me!
吃子弹吧
Meet the twins!
来吧 福特
All right, Ford!
咱们俩对决吧
Just you and me, baby!
你不该欺负女生
Shouldn't pick on girls.
你没事吧？
You all right?
我骑车从急驶列车的车顶跳下来
I just jumped my bike onto the roof of a moving train.
人在危急时能激发神奇的潜能
It's amazing what you can do when you have no choice.
小威跟小刀呢？
Where are Val and DaIton?
他赢了我 我差点就没命
He had me, dog. He had me. I was gone!
他却及时救我一命
He's the one snatched me up out of there!
我搞不懂 他不像是凶手
I'm trying to figure out why. He ain't acting like no killer!
我只知道你小弟挂了 他在逃亡
Your brother's dead and cracker's on the run.
我觉得不太对劲 这整件事感觉怪怪的
Shit don't feel right. Don't sound right, don't look right.
只有抓到他才能搞清楚
Only way we can find out is to get our hands on him.
- 我同意 - 那就快出发吧
- I'm with that. - Then get your black ass up and let's go!
大伙儿走吧
Everybody, let's go!
小威第一次骑得比你快
First time Val's beat you anywhere!
你一定是被女人耽误了
Must be the chick.
是啊 我停下来修个指甲
Yeah, I stopped for a manicure.
你要听坏消息吗？每一条公路都有临检站
Want this hour's bad news? Every major road in L.A. is blocked.
你说太容易就不好玩
I know you said it wouldn't be any fun if it was easy...
可是也不需要这样玩命吧
but does it have to be this much fun?
你要怎么替我脱罪？
You said you could make this go away. How?
有时候证人很健忘
Sometimes witnesses forget what they saw.
或是拒绝作证
Refuse to testify.
等我回洛杉矶…
You still want your shit back...
再把货还给你 明天下午三点
I'll call you when I get to L.A. 3:00 tomorrow afternoon.
干嘛？
What?
事情有点不对劲 福特不像杀人凶手
Jay, something doesn't sit with me. Ford doesn't profile up as a killer.
你的直觉真灵光 韩德森
Yeah? Good instincts, Henderson.
半年前我给福特一次机会 他却落跑了
Listen, I gave Ford a chance to tell the truth six months ago. He ran.
昨晚我再次给他机会 他又落跑
I gave him another chance last night. He ran again.
无辜的人是不会落跑的
Innocent men, Henderson, don't run.
他上钩了
He went for it!
现在只要躲过几百个警察就行
Now we just gotta get past the several hundred cops between us and L.A.
希望你这次是计划好了
God, I hope you have a plan this time.
我是有计划
Yeah, I got a plan.
你们想撇下我吗？
You gonna leave without me?
我的老天
Oh, my God.
你们看
Check it out, man.
哇塞
Holy shit.
看到三个飚车族跟一个小妞吗？
Seen three bikers and a chick on a couple of crotch rockets in the last hour?
这儿的人都蠢到极点
Must be something in the water up here.
我说的话你一定听不懂
Okay. Words strung together into sentences obviously bewilder you.
让我再说一次
Let me try again.
三个男的…
Three dudes...
一个女的…
a girl...
两台摩托车
and a couple of bikes.
- 不知道 有很多卡车司机 - 是吗？
- Don't know. Seen a lot of truckers. - Really?
有一个妞儿
One girl.
- 她的身材超火辣 - 闭嘴
- Man, you should've seen the pair... - Shut up.
监看摄影机有用吗？
Does this thing work?
福特 你有病吗？
Ford. What is wrong with you?
抱歉
Sorry.
- 坏了吗？- 对
- Is it fried? - Yeah.
你没说你为什么选择去泰国
So you never actually told me why you chose Thailand.
我想去个不会让我想起你的地方
Well, I just wanted to go someplace that wouldn't remind me of you.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
结果有用吗？
How did that work out for you?
- 没什么用 - 是吗？
- Not real well. - No?
承认吧
Oh, come on, admit it.
你很高兴我回来
You're so glad I came back.
我只是这周末闲着没事干
I just had nothing better to do this weekend.
高速公路上干嘛忽然停车？
Why we stopping in the middle of the interstate?
临检站
Roadblock.
你可以走了 开车吧
Sir! You're clear. Go ahead. Move it out.
这个好了 让下一辆过来
Go ahead and send the next one!
检查倒数第二辆车
Check the second one back!
- 你好 警察先生 - 请你下车
- Good evening, officer. - Could you step out of the vehicle, please.
- 有问题吗？- 没有 只是例行临检
- There a problem? - No, sir. Just a routine check.
- 请你打开货柜 - 没问题
- You mind opening her up? - No, not at all.
- 你打哪儿来？- 巴斯托镇
- Where you coming from? - Barstow.
- 那儿没下大雨 - 是啊 只下点小雨
- Much drier in Barstow. - Yeah, just a little.
艾德 这么快就回来了？
Hey, Ed! What are you doing back so soon?
明晚我在洛城有一场比赛
I got a race in L.A. tomorrow night.
他没问题 他是赛车界的英雄
He's all right. Regular hero here on the local circuit.
- 让他过去吧 - 是的
- Let him through. - Yes, sir.
艾德 祝明天好运
Hey, Ed, good luck tomorrow night.
- 走吧 - 谢了
- Beat it. - Thanks, Frank.
福特应该打电话来了
Ford should've called us by now.
他这一路很顺 别紧张
He's just having a good run. Don't sweat it, man.
要是福特不合作…
We got over a mil riding on this!
拿不到一百万的货 我就得坐牢
We're looking at life in prison if Ford doesn't go down as planned.
别叫我不要紧张
Don't tell me not to sweat it.
吃你的糖去 给我闭上狗嘴
So grab yourseIf a candy bar and shut your mouth.
好拉风的机车 超酷的
That's a sweet hog, man. Look at that beast!
飚车万岁 或比手势
Live to ride. Or that. Yeah.
可以让我们拍张相吗？
Could we get a picture of you guys?
我们在旅行 我们要把照片寄给各地网友
We're on a road trip, we e-mail people on our buddy list where we're at.
可以吗？谁是小情侣？
Could we do that? Who's in love?
- 他们是 - 就在那
- They are. - Right there.
笑一个 有点人样
Give me a big smile, like you guys are human.
他眨眼 她也眨眼 再拍一次
He blinked and she blinked. Look at this. Let's do it again.
这次不要眨眼哦
This time, no blinking.
笑一个
Smile.
又怎么了？
Now what?
你要懂得如何理财
It's also about financial freedom.
- 需要帮忙吗？- 把货柜打开
- What can I do for you? - Why don't you open up the back for me.
这辆卡车好长
That's a long truck.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
- 奇怪了 - 什么？
- That's weird. - What?
锁不见了
My lock's gone.
你在等绿灯吗？
You waiting for a green light?
- 让一让 - 卡车抛锚 叫拖吊车
- Let's go, make a hole! - Truck's broke. Call a tow truck.
- 好了没？- 上车 我来开
- Are you done? - Get in. I'm driving.
死警察
Fuck the police!
- 那是威胁吗？- 应该是
- Was that a threat? - I think it was.
前面塞车
Ford, traffic!
所以我才讨厌开车
This is why I hate four wheels.
你先逃走
Hey, you're gonna have to make a break!
- 我们一起逃 - 你跟小威带夏恩逃走
- We go together! - No, you and Val can get Shane out of this!
不要 我要跟你走
No way, I'm going with you!
- 你不能跟我 - 你真可恶
- No, you're not. - Goddamn it, Ford!
我就知道你喜欢我
I always knew you had a thing for me.
快把她带走
Get her out of here!
喂
Hey!
小心
Watch out.
我不能忍受 我要把机车退回去 你把机车收回去
And I'm not gonna stand for it. I wanna return the bike. You can take it back.
我不能退是什么意思？我才骑了二百多里
What do you mean I can't bring it back? Okay, there's only 200 miles on the bike.
你敢再说…
If you say one more word....
王八蛋
Asshole!
喂？他又挂我电话
Hello? Hung up again!
- 臭飚车族 - 你疯了 快叫支援
- Bikers. - This is crazy! We can call backup.
你不喜欢我开车 就去搭顺风车
If you don't like my driving, Henderson, you can get out and hitch.
不是吧
No way!
幸好有安全气囊 别说话
Thank God for airbags. Shut up.
- 来吧 福特 - 你误会我了
- Come on, Ford. - You got this wrong!
哎呀
Damn!
妈的 疯白人
Damn! Crazy white boy!
我不想…
Look, man, I don't wanna...
你够种跟我单挑吗？
You think you man enough to drop that hammer?
我不想 朱利尔也不是我杀的
Don't want to. I didn't kill Junior either.
如果是的话 我就不会救你一命
If I did, I would've let you die at the tracks.
- 你为什么不跟我解释？- 我想你一定不会听
- Why didn't you stick around and talk? - I didn't think this would go all that well.
好吧 他是谁杀的？
All right. You didn't kill him, who did?
是亨利 他陷害我
Henry James. He set me up.
你要我相信你的话？
So I'm supposed to just believe what you say now?
你等着瞧 我会逮到他
Well, see for yourseIf. I'm taking him down.
到时候你不相信 再毙了我
You don't believe me, you can always shoot me then.
你掉了这玩意
You dropped this.
这最好是好消息
This better be someone with good news or money.
我可以让你逮到凶手 同时把毒品交给你
What would you say if I gave you Junior's killer and Henry's drugs at the same time?
哪里？
Where?
你知道地方 半年前你抄过她的店
You know the address. You busted its doors down about six months ago.
两小时后见
Meet me there in two hours.
安非他命
Crystal meth.
你能不能帮帮忙？
I don't suppose we got a spare set of hands?
- 干嘛？- 什么干嘛
- Yeah? - Don't "yeah" me.
有什么动静？
How we doing over there?
只有我跟一大堆鱼
It's just me and the fishes, man.
有美人鱼我会通知你
If a mermaid pops up, I'll call you.
- 待在道尔顿那儿 - 好
- Just stay there at Dalton's. - Yeah.
这儿真舒适
It's lovely here.
过一会儿见
I'll see you in a little while.
小心点 好吗？
Just be careful, all right?
- 你知道我的 - 所以我才会担心
- Well, you know me. - Yeah, that's why I'm worried.
搞定了我再打给你
I'll call you when it's over.
- 会是什么人？- 我叫了披萨
- Who the hell is that? - I ordered pizza.
- 不会吧？- 真的
- You're kidding me, right? - No.
- 你不是开玩笑 - 我一紧张就想吃
- You're not kidding? - I eat when I'm nervous.
他随时都想吃 他是爱吃鬼
He eats when he's horny. He just likes to eat.
你好吗？
How you doing?
我看他是不会来了
Seems like your boy ain't coming.
现在怎么办？
Now what?
他一定会来 相信我
He'll be here. Trust me.
如果我要拿回价值百万的毒品…
Tell me you got a million dollars' worth of my ice?
我一定会准时
I'd try to be punctual.
你又不是亨利
You ain't Henry.
他一定会来
He'll be here.
我这人不是很有耐心
You know, I ain't exactly known for my patience.
- 这是什么？- Y2K
- What's this? - Y2K.
全世界最快的机车
Fastest bike in the world.
碳合金底盘 劳斯莱斯型号直升机喷射引擎
Carbon-fiber chassis buiIt around a Rolls-Royce jet helicopter engine.
十秒内能加速到200里
Zero to 200 in less than 10 seconds, huh?
我听说过
I heard of these.
- 这台车有什么问题？- 它不是我的
- What's wrong with this one? - I don't own it.
- FBI 手举起来 - 手放在头后面
- FBI! Hands where I can see them! - Drop it. Hands behind your head.
- 你想陷害我 - 他们是来抓亨利的
- You tried to set me up. - They're here for Henry.
枪放到地上 把它滑过来
Put the gun on the ground and slide it to me, now.
你要等亨利来才现身 你在警校没学过吗？
You're supposed to wait for Henry. Didn't you learn anything in FBI school?
给我闭嘴
Ford, shut up.
这是亨利的机车？
Those Henry's bikes?
- 对 - 安非他命在里面？
- Yeah. - And the meth's inside them?
- 没错 - 嗯…
- Yeah. - Then...
干得好
nice work.
喂 霹雳女警
Hey. Nancy Drew.
不 别开枪 住手
"No. Don't shoot. Stop."
这真是一场悲剧
What a sad and sudden tragedy.
射得真准 这样的话…
Nice shot, by the way. Seriously. So now...
我又可以嫁祸给你
I get to pin this murder on you...
因为大家都知道你杀了朱利尔
and, well, everyone knows you killed Junior...
现在我可以杀你们了
so now I can shoot you both.
- 干 - 是啊
- Shit. - Yeah.
- 我该先杀谁呢？- 他 先杀他
- Which one of you guys wants to go first? - Him. Shoot him first.
你确定毒品在里头吗？
You sure the drugs are in there?
- 喂 - 我埋了炸药
- Hey. - They're wired.
你不放下枪 大家就死在一起
You put the gun on the ground or we all go up.
是我女友 对不起
It's my girIfriend. Excuse me. Sorry.
宝贝 我很好
Hey, baby. I'm fine.
你就进来吧
Why don't you come in? All right.
你们一定会喜欢她
You're gonna love her.
这是我的老相好
Meet my partner.
你真的以为我会上当吗？
Did you really think I was stupid enough to walk into a trap?
等等
Wait.
打声招呼吧
Say hello, bitch.
夏恩
Shane.
你们看这是谁
Look who it is.
你要跟你小弟在阴间团聚
Guess the lunch line's gonna be a little shorter at family reunions.
黑小子
Huh, dog?
我早就该毙了你
I should have done your ass when I did your bitch brother.
是啊 没错
Yeah, you should have.
真的吗？
Really?
看来这是一个僵局
All right. It seems we have ourselves a little dilemma.
你不把毒品给我 我就把你女友的脑袋轰掉
Give me my meth or your little girIfriend is gonna redefine the term "airhead."
放下引爆器
Now, drop that switch.
谁晓得呢？
Who knows, baby?
也许她跟我混久了 就不想回到福特身边
After a little time with us, she might not wanna go back to Ford.
不用急 时间多的是
Go ahead, take a moment. We have plenty of time.
请求警力支援
Requesting backup at 2000 North Alameda Street.
谢了
Thanks.
不
No, no, no!
等等
Hey, wait!
你这是恶有恶报
Now, ain't that ironic?
- 你没事吧？- 没事 亨利呢？
- You okay? - Yeah. Where's Henry?
- 我要找回那台机车 - 我要去修理那臭婆娘
- I gotta get that bike. - I gotta get that bitch.
没错
Damn right.
- 两位大哥没事吧？- 好痛
- You Power Rangers all right? - That hurt.
- 喂 - 杰
- Hey. - Jay!
我穿了防弹背心
Bulletproof vest, asshole.
可恶 快走
Shit! Let's go!
你一直都是个混球
You were always a punk.
- 你想逃吗？- 你想单挑吗？
- Going somewhere? - You want some of this, bitch?
我就等你这句话
Oh, I thought you'd never ask.
你不该惹老娘的
You messed with the wrong chick!
你才不该惹毛我 臭婆娘
Looks like you did, bitch.
要我载一程吗？
Need a ride?
- 你没事吧？- 死不了
- You all right? - I'll live.
亨利的齿盘 跟凶器吻合
This is Henry's sprocket. It should match the chain...
你朋友说过了 待会再说好吗？
Your friends just told me. Could we maybe do this later?
死了一大堆白人
All these dead white folks around here.
你跟我扯平了
So it look like we done, huh?
- 我为你老弟感到遗憾 - 是啊
- I'm sorry about your brother. - Yeah.
我得走人 我跟警察不对盘
I gotta get out of here. Me and Johnny Law ain't on a first-name basis.
喂
Hey.
- 干嘛？- 谢了
- What? - Thanks.
不用谢 帮我一个忙
Don't sweat it, man. Just do me one favor.
- 什么？- 别闯入我的地盘
- What's that? - Keep your ass out of Inglewood.
我在这世上只有这家店
This shop was the only thing in the world that was really mine.
我可是存了好久的钱才顶下来
Do you have any idea how long it took me to save up for it?
对不起
I'm sorry, Shane.
你脱罪了 也得到你要的了
You're in the clear, so I guess you got what you wanted.
我要的只有你
You're looking at the only reason that I came back.
我只想跟你在一起
I'm betting on more days like that.
你能为我做一件事 福特
You know what you could do for me, Ford?
带我到墨西哥
Take me to Mexico.
- 我们往哪个方向？- 南方
- Where we heading? - South.
我要去接一个人
I got someone to pick up.
狂飚吧
Let's ride.